GUSTI MUHAMMAD ADZAKY

Freshgraduate Software Developer

Pontianak, Indonesia | HP: +6289691789422 | Email: gmadzaky@gmail.com

RINGKASAN

A software developer, a Bachelor of Informatics Engineering graduate from Universitas Muhammadiyah Pontianak in 2023, with over 2 years of experience in developing web and applications. I enjoy working in teams and consistently seek opportunities to expand my skills with every project I undertake. One of my main focuses is on web and mobile application development. I believe that by continuously learning and honing my skills, I will gain valuable experience to grow as a professional.

PENGALAMAN

UNIVERSITAS MUHAMMADIYAH PONTIANAK - Pontianak, Indonesia

MC(Master of Ceremonies) (November 2021 - November 2022)

- Presenter for the Informatics Engineering Program at Universitas Muhammadiyah Pontianak.
- Host of a talk show discussing the latest web technologies with Sandhika Galih (Gemini Developer, Lecturer, Youtuber).
- Moderator for the guest lecture on selected topics in Software Engineering.

PT PUTRA KREASI HOTAMA - Pontianak, Indonesia

Internship (Maret 2022 - May 2022)

- Created a Restful API and web-based Admin Dashboard for the simulation of a podcast feature in the Qara'a application using CODEIGNITER4.
- Developed the user interface and layout using Android Studio (Kotlin) for the 25 Prophets feature.

J&T Pontianak - Pontianak, Indonesia

Developer for TSP Optimization using Genetic Algorithm at J&T Pontianak for couriers (January 2022 - February 2023)

Developed from web interface design to completion, including UI/UX and wireframing using Figma, implemented login features, developed CRUD functions on the dashboard, including cost estimation menu, data integration via Google Maps API, and map visualization to solve the Traveling Salesman Problem.

FREELANCER - Pontianak, Indonesia

Web developer (October 2021 - February 2024)

I have been a freelancer in e-commerce website development since October 2021 until February 2024. During this period, I have successfully completed several significant projects, including:

- Margalas.com (Okt '23 Feb '24): Developed an e-commerce web application with features such as a Laravel-authenticated UI dashboard, admin and customer role management, Dom Pdf integration, Captcha implementation, and Cronjob settings for monthly database maintenance.
- **RSUD Purwokerto's Nutrition Catering** (Jan '22 Mar '22): Designed a website using PHP Native, providing CRUD on the admin dashboard, and integrating ordering features via WhatsApp.
- Rabbani Store's E-commerce (Nov '21 Feb '22): Developed an e-commerce platform using Codeigniter with authentication system, simple payment integration, Raja Ongkir API integration, email delivery, and invoice creation with TCPDF.
- Consultant for Implementing Traveling Salesman Problem Optimization using Genetic Algorithm in various web-based case studies with Google Maps API (June '24 -Present): Assisted in implementing the Genetic Algorithm model.

PENDIDIKAN

UNIVERSITAS MUHAMMADIYAH PONTIANAK (2018 - 2023)

Bachelor of Informatics Engineering - GPA 3.41

KEMAMPUAN

- **Programming Languages:** PHP (Laravel, Codeigniter, PHP Native)
- Programming Languages: JavaScript (React, Vue, jQuery, Alpine.js)
- Programming Languages: python (streamlit)
- Databases: Sql
- Public Speaking